<resources>
        <string name="app_name">SPS Radio</string>
        <string name="text_more">More</string>
        <string name="text_journal">Journal</string>
        <string name="text_radio">Radio</string>
        <string name="text_tv">TV</string>
        <string name="text_program">Program</string>
        <string name="journal_text">JazznBluesExperience is your channel for all the best jazz and blues music. Find your favorite songs and artists and experience the best of jazz music and blues music. Subscribe for free to stay</string>
        <string name="drawer_open">Drawer Open</string>
        <string name="drawer_close">Drawer Close</string>
        <string name="program1_text">Useful dummy for fans of iron horses. What worries, disturbs or just about the world of achievements in the field of speed and environmental friendliness of the car. All the most interesting for motorists in the author\'s program from Gordianiak Maxim. Your car deserves your knowledge of the world of iron!</string>
        <string name="program1_title_text">Road without a rod</string>
        <string name="program1_duration">10 automobile minutes</string>
        <string name="program2_title_text">Morning should be good</string>
        <string name="program2_duration">1 happy hour</string>
        <string name="program2_text">The morning program for the happiness of a new day, for creating your good mood and charging you with cleaning techniques from bad thoughts. a program that will make you believe in happiness and its manifestations in a variety of life forms! You can enjoy great music and listen to an astrological forecast for the whole day. You can convey greetings and wish from a person of the very best of people a good day and admire your feelings to them! After all, it is the support of loved ones who plays the most powerful role in shaping your outlook! Create and pass a good particle to the whole of Ukraine! Make your morning positive with us on the wave of good from Butterfljak!</string>
        <string name="program3_title_text">History or how it was all</string>
        <string name="program3_duration">15–20 incredibly interesting minutes</string>
        <string name="program3_text">Every day in the past, something has happened, be aware of the world and pay tribute to those who made the world better for you! Transmission, about the incredible wonders of the world every day. And the world is, in fact, boundless, it is necessary to know it together.</string>
        <string name="program4_title_text">Melody that loves you</string>
        <string name="program4_duration">40 minutes</string>
        <string name="program4_text">What causes your blood to move faster, it\'s easy to feel the will and the mood to snap over. The best hits that accompany you throughout your life, you just have to admire them.</string>
        <string name="program5_title_text">The world of news</string>
        <string name="program5_duration">10 information minutes</string>
        <string name="program6_title_text">Delicious lunch</string>
        <string name="program6_duration">1 hour</string>
        <string name="program6_text">In order for all this to happen, it is necessary to expedite all greetings. Do not let the routine of the working day take you completely. How do you imagine it, so call and write to me and we\'ll file it together). Birthday, holidays and just a positive one should be noted and rejoice at that. Your positive energy will happily make a smile on your loved ones, never forget about them.</string>
        <string name="program7_title_text">Travel for the soul</string>
        <string name="program7_duration">20 minutes</string>
        <string name="program7_text">The rest is good, the main thing is not to forget about his favor. How, where and in general you should visit Ukraine you will tell Radio Butterfljaka. Honor the nature, protect what it has created and enrich itself with energy for a happy life.</string>
        <string name="program8_title_text">Take care of yourself</string>
        <string name="program8_text">Give your loved one a romantic evening. Gather your thoughts into one fractal. You know what it is worth. The author\'s program about goodness, warm smiles and comfort of a blanket from your favorite radio!</string>
        <string name="program9_title_text">Sports minute</string>
        <string name="program10_title_text">The transition of consiousness</string>
        <string name="program10_duration">1 hour</string>
        <string name="program10_text">The only one in its kind is the author\'s program on purifying the body, understanding its inner self. Correct music and meditation. All about happiness and its manifestations. A yoga of thought that will change your life forever. Become better, believe the energy of the body and soul is more important than material things. How to do this, our author Maxim knows. \ "This harmony in nature, I will only show it to you … \"</string>
        <string name="program11_title_text">Evening chairs</string>
        <string name="program11_duration">1 hour</string>
        <string name="program11_text">The evening quietly came and you are already at home? Fine tune in for relaxation and wish you all the lucky evening. A greetings program for those who value their loved ones.</string>
        <string name="program12_title_text">And this was in my life …</string>
        <string name="program12_duration">30 minutes</string>
        <string name="program12_text">The most interesting inventions that made the world change. The most incredible stories from the lives of your idols and just incredible in this infinite. What and what to keep in mind is the author\'s transmission on the waves of the radio, which honors the achievement.</string>
        <string name="business_radio_title">SPS Radio</string>
        <string name="text_exit">Exit the program</string>
    <!--<string name="media_url_mp3">http://lin3.ash.fast-serv.com:6026/stream_96</string>-->
    <string name="media_url_mp3">http://radiottl.ddns.net:8000/timeradio</string>
    <string name="ticker_text">SPS Radio playing</string>
    <string name="notification_title">SPS Radio playing music</string>
</resources>
